[Rock music]
What is needed is that it is cold, preferably that it has been a bit in the freezer before.
So you should take everything around.
So you just pull on this one.
Listen damn careful now, because you will be learned something like this educational before.
This little ... where you see that the bottle is sealed, the seam yes.
Well said
Are you sitting backing my brother here now, is that what you are doing
[Laughter] No then
I turned years yesterday, and it ended with a fight between me and my brother, you can say.
But it always ends so when I'm with my brother and drink.
He knows exactly which buttons to press, so I get started on all cylinders
I have a bump on my arm today because he hit me so hard.
And mom says:
[Light, dedicated voice] "But it wasn't that hard"
I have too damn bruise and bump today, of course it was hard
We try to plan here, after all,
Because today we are going ... magnetic fishing I forgot for the fuck the magnet at home!
No?
- Yes, haha!
[Laugh]
I came on it now
I don't know, it feels like ... maybe you should throw it far out.
Then you pull it in a little.
The premiere
Now we bowl and hope we ... you can get rich in this
Yes maybe.
Be careful not to spill the beer.
Good consistency splash.
- Yes.
Take in now take in as hell!
Don't drop it so the whole rope disappears.
[Cries and laughter]
We got not a shit.
No f*tta, I dropped it.
Released it-no!
It's on
What
-—-—-
[Roar]
It's still on!
- It is certainly kind of a buoy or something so boring.
There is something red
[Screams] It's a bike
Nah
[Loudly] Well what!
What
It is probably Sweden's absolute best film.
[Shot]
xxx
Don't F*ck with Benny the cop.
Benny
[Inaudible Slud] Benny
You can find something
No...
[Laugh]
Oh God...
Where did you get this idea from
You should invent it.
Hurry you fast as hell before I do.
Takes patents on the shit.
Grab how many people fished for Kim Kardashians Diamond Earrings.
I think they found it!
- did them?
Crying Kim Kardashian over an earring, then it is expensive as hell.
Then it's not free
Damn what you got to take in when you pulled it up there
It sucked.
Check.
- Sick!
If you have come this far now go in and subscriba, lay and comment!
What would you have wanted to get up,
What the hell do i know, write something cute
Otherwise, you get a hit.
Are you kidding or so ... the decor- I can post some pictures here, if I even want to show ...
This is naked after all
Now I feel naked.
My first apartment was over here so we were always on Hamngatan and drank beer.
That is why we are Tjenis with those who work there.
Stammis.
- Stammis!
Old stammer.
The tribal price of beer, then you know that you have succeeded in life
That's the only thing I want to achieve.
We have just stopped in a little jaw, loaded the camera,
Drunk some Irish Coffee.
Should we try to find any magnetic fish
[Laugh]
Bowl
You have fixed a man for me now
Dense as hell.
- Dense as hell.
Excavator operator.
- Oh, and good looking too.
Scooter cross, excavator, handy and dense.
It's like the hand in the glove.
He has sheep and lambs too.
- And have sheep and lambs.
Is he lamb?
- Yes.
He is as old as me.
- I thought you would say like us.
Perfect after all.
98a
But he has to fall in love with me too, how should he fall in love with me
Is he in love with me
Yes a little?
Beetled
But there is a difference between being hungry and in love.
He must fall in love.
He can probably be.
Can't all comment on a tip on getting someone to fall in love with one.
Do you have any advice
I hear it now ...
[Laugh]
What should I say?
- [mimic] I hear it now myself.
[Says in different ways] I hear it now myself.
I hear it myself now.
[Mimics] "self"
How should I get commas instead of point
No, sit.
There was no point, it was coming.
Well that's point ...
... ...
[Sings]